- id: k-joyo-611b
  prompt: "Meanings: love, affection, favourite\nOnyomi: アイ\nKunyomi: いと.しい, かな.しい, め.でる, お.しむ"
  answers:
    - 愛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6848
  prompt: "Meanings: plan, suggestion, draft\nOnyomi: アン\nKunyomi: つくえ"
  answers:
    - 案
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ee5
  prompt: "Meanings: by means of, because, in view of\nOnyomi: イ\nKunyomi: もっ.て"
  answers:
    - 以
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8863
  prompt: "Meanings: garment, clothes, dressing\nOnyomi: イ, エ\nKunyomi: ころも, きぬ, -ぎ"
  answers:
    - 衣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f4d
  prompt: "Meanings: rank, grade, throne\nOnyomi: イ\nKunyomi: くらい, ぐらい"
  answers:
    - 位
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8328
  prompt: "Meanings: briar, thorn\nOnyomi: シ, ジ\nKunyomi: いばら, かや, くさぶき"
  answers:
    - 茨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5370
  prompt: "Meanings: stamp, seal, mark\nOnyomi: イン\nKunyomi: しるし, -じるし, しる.す"
  answers:
    - 印
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-82f1
  prompt: "Meanings: England, English, hero\nOnyomi: エイ\nKunyomi: はなぶさ"
  answers:
    - 英
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6804
  prompt: "Meanings: flourish, prosperity, honor\nOnyomi: エイ, ヨウ\nKunyomi: さか.える, は.え, -ば.え, は.える"
  answers:
    - 栄
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5a9b
  prompt: "Meanings: beautiful woman, princess\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: ひめ"
  answers:
    - 媛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5869
  prompt: "Meanings: salt\nOnyomi: エン\nKunyomi: しお"
  answers:
    - 塩
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5ca1
  prompt: "Meanings: mount, hill, knoll\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: おか"
  answers:
    - 岡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5104
  prompt: "Meanings: hundred million, 10**8\nOnyomi: オク"
  answers:
    - 億
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-52a0
  prompt: "Meanings: add, addition, increase\nOnyomi: カ\nKunyomi: くわ.える, くわ.わる"
  answers:
    - 加
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-679c
  prompt: "Meanings: fruit, reward, carry out\nOnyomi: カ\nKunyomi: は.たす, はた.す, -は.たす, は.てる"
  answers:
    - 果
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8ca8
  prompt: "Meanings: freight, goods, property\nOnyomi: カ\nKunyomi: たから"
  answers:
    - 貨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8ab2
  prompt: "Meanings: chapter, lesson, section\nOnyomi: カ"
  answers:
    - 課
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-82bd
  prompt: "Meanings: bud, sprout, spear\nOnyomi: ガ\nKunyomi: め"
  answers:
    - 芽
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8cc0
  prompt: "Meanings: congratulations, joy\nOnyomi: ガ"
  answers:
    - 賀
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6539
  prompt: "Meanings: reformation, change, modify\nOnyomi: カイ\nKunyomi: あらた.める, あらた.まる"
  answers:
    - 改
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-68b0
  prompt: "Meanings: contraption, fetter, machine\nOnyomi: カイ\nKunyomi: かせ"
  answers:
    - 械
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5bb3
  prompt: "Meanings: harm, injury\nOnyomi: ガイ"
  answers:
    - 害
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8857
  prompt: "Meanings: boulevard, street, town\nOnyomi: ガイ, カイ\nKunyomi: まち"
  answers:
    - 街
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5404
  prompt: "Meanings: each, every, either\nOnyomi: カク\nKunyomi: おのおの"
  answers:
    - 各
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-899a
  prompt: "Meanings: memorize, learn, remember\nOnyomi: カク\nKunyomi: おぼ.える, さ.ます, さ.める, さと.る"
  answers:
    - 覚
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6f5f
  prompt: "Meanings: lagoon\nOnyomi: セキ\nKunyomi: かた, -がた"
  answers:
    - 潟
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b8c
  prompt: "Meanings: perfect, completion, end\nOnyomi: カン"
  answers:
    - 完
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b98
  prompt: "Meanings: bureaucrat, the government, organ\nOnyomi: カン"
  answers:
    - 官
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7ba1
  prompt: "Meanings: pipe, tube, wind instrument\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: くだ"
  answers:
    - 管
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-95a2
  prompt: "Meanings: connection, barrier, gateway\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: せき, -ぜき, かか.わる, からくり"
  answers:
    - 関
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-89b3
  prompt: "Meanings: outlook, look, appearance\nOnyomi: カン\nKunyomi: み.る, しめ.す"
  answers:
    - 観
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9858
  prompt: "Meanings: petition, request, vow\nOnyomi: ガン\nKunyomi: ねが.う, -ねがい"
  answers:
    - 願
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5c90
  prompt: "Meanings: branch off, fork in road, scene\nOnyomi: キ, ギ"
  answers:
    - 岐
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e0c
  prompt: "Meanings: hope, beg, request\nOnyomi: キ, ケ\nKunyomi: まれ, こいねが.う"
  answers:
    - 希
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b63
  prompt: "Meanings: seasons\nOnyomi: キ"
  answers:
    - 季
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-65d7
  prompt: "Meanings: national flag, banner, standard\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: はた"
  answers:
    - 旗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5668
  prompt: "Meanings: utensil, vessel, receptacle\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: うつわ"
  answers:
    - 器
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6a5f
  prompt: "Meanings: loom, mechanism, machine\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: はた"
  answers:
    - 機
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8b70
  prompt: "Meanings: deliberation, consultation, debate\nOnyomi: ギ"
  answers:
    - 議
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6c42
  prompt: "Meanings: request, want, wish for\nOnyomi: キュウ, グ\nKunyomi: もと.める"
  answers:
    - 求
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6ce3
  prompt: "Meanings: cry, weep, moan\nOnyomi: キュウ\nKunyomi: な.く"
  answers:
    - 泣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d66
  prompt: "Meanings: salary, wage, gift\nOnyomi: キュウ\nKunyomi: たま.う, たも.う, -たま.え"
  answers:
    - 給
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6319
  prompt: "Meanings: raise, plan, project\nOnyomi: キョ\nKunyomi: あ.げる, あ.がる, こぞ.る"
  answers:
    - 挙
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6f01
  prompt: "Meanings: fishing, fishery\nOnyomi: ギョ, リョウ\nKunyomi: あさ.る"
  answers:
    - 漁
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5171
  prompt: "Meanings: together, both, neither\nOnyomi: キョウ\nKunyomi: とも, とも.に, -ども"
  answers:
    - 共
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5354
  prompt: "Meanings: co-, cooperation\nOnyomi: キョウ"
  answers:
    - 協
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-93e1
  prompt: "Meanings: mirror, speculum, barrel-head\nOnyomi: キョウ, ケイ\nKunyomi: かがみ"
  answers:
    - 鏡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7af6
  prompt: "Meanings: emulate, compete with, bid\nOnyomi: キョウ, ケイ\nKunyomi: きそ.う, せ.る, くら.べる"
  answers:
    - 競
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6975
  prompt: "Meanings: extreme, pole, extremely\nOnyomi: キョク, ゴク\nKunyomi: きわ.める, きわ.まる, きわ.まり, きわ.み"
  answers:
    - 極
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-718a
  prompt: "Meanings: bear\nOnyomi: ユウ\nKunyomi: くま"
  answers:
    - 熊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a13
  prompt: "Meanings: instruction, Japanese character reading, explanation\nOnyomi: クン, キン\nKunyomi: おし.える, よ.む, くん.ずる"
  answers:
    - 訓
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8ecd
  prompt: "Meanings: army, force, troops\nOnyomi: グン\nKunyomi: いくさ"
  answers:
    - 軍
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-90e1
  prompt: "Meanings: county, district\nOnyomi: グン\nKunyomi: こおり"
  answers:
    - 郡
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7fa4
  prompt: "Meanings: flock, group, crowd\nOnyomi: グン\nKunyomi: む.れる, む.れ, むら, むら.がる"
  answers:
    - 群
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5f84
  prompt: "Meanings: diameter, path, method\nOnyomi: ケイ\nKunyomi: みち, こみち, さしわたし, ただちに"
  answers:
    - 径
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-666f
  prompt: "Meanings: scenery, view\nOnyomi: ケイ"
  answers:
    - 景
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-82b8
  prompt: "Meanings: technique, art, craft\nOnyomi: ゲイ, ウン\nKunyomi: う.える, のり, わざ"
  answers:
    - 芸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6b20
  prompt: "Meanings: lack, gap, fail\nOnyomi: ケツ, ケン\nKunyomi: か.ける, か.く"
  answers:
    - 欠
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d50
  prompt: "Meanings: tie, bind, contract\nOnyomi: ケツ, ケチ\nKunyomi: むす.ぶ, ゆ.う, ゆ.わえる"
  answers:
    - 結
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5efa
  prompt: "Meanings: build\nOnyomi: ケン, コン\nKunyomi: た.てる, た.て, -だ.て, た.つ"
  answers:
    - 建
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5065
  prompt: "Meanings: healthy, health, strength\nOnyomi: ケン\nKunyomi: すこ.やか"
  answers:
    - 健
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9a13
  prompt: "Meanings: verification, effect, testing\nOnyomi: ケン, ゲン\nKunyomi: あかし, しるし, ため.す, ためし"
  answers:
    - 験
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-56fa
  prompt: "Meanings: harden, set, clot\nOnyomi: コ\nKunyomi: かた.める, かた.まる, かた.まり, かた.い"
  answers:
    - 固
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-529f
  prompt: "Meanings: achievement, merits, success\nOnyomi: コウ, ク\nKunyomi: いさお"
  answers:
    - 功
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-597d
  prompt: "Meanings: fond, pleasing, like something\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: この.む, す.く, よ.い, い.い"
  answers:
    - 好
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9999
  prompt: "Meanings: incense, smell, perfume\nOnyomi: コウ, キョウ\nKunyomi: か, かお.り, かお.る"
  answers:
    - 香
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5019
  prompt: "Meanings: climate, season, weather\nOnyomi: コウ\nKunyomi: そうろう"
  answers:
    - 候
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5eb7
  prompt: "Meanings: ease, peace\nOnyomi: コウ"
  answers:
    - 康
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f50
  prompt: "Meanings: assistant, help\nOnyomi: サ"
  answers:
    - 佐
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5dee
  prompt: "Meanings: distinction, difference, variation\nOnyomi: サ\nKunyomi: さ.す, さ.し"
  answers:
    - 差
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-83dc
  prompt: "Meanings: vegetable, side dish, greens\nOnyomi: サイ\nKunyomi: な"
  answers:
    - 菜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6700
  prompt: "Meanings: utmost, most, extreme\nOnyomi: サイ, シュ\nKunyomi: もっと.も, つま"
  answers:
    - 最
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-57fc
  prompt: "Meanings: cape, spit, promontory\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: さき, さい, みさき"
  answers:
    - 埼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6750
  prompt: "Meanings: lumber, log, timber\nOnyomi: ザイ"
  answers:
    - 材
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5d0e
  prompt: "Meanings: promontory, cape, spit\nOnyomi: キ\nKunyomi: さき, さい, みさき"
  answers:
    - 崎
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6628
  prompt: "Meanings: yesterday, previous\nOnyomi: サク"
  answers:
    - 昨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-672d
  prompt: "Meanings: tag, paper money, counter for bonds\nOnyomi: サツ\nKunyomi: ふだ"
  answers:
    - 札
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5237
  prompt: "Meanings: printing, print, brush\nOnyomi: サツ\nKunyomi: す.る, -ず.り, -ずり, は.く"
  answers:
    - 刷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5bdf
  prompt: "Meanings: guess, presume, surmise\nOnyomi: サツ"
  answers:
    - 察
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-53c2
  prompt: "Meanings: nonplussed, three (in documents), going\nOnyomi: サン, シン\nKunyomi: まい.る, まい-, まじわる, みつ"
  answers:
    - 参
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7523
  prompt: "Meanings: products, bear, give birth\nOnyomi: サン\nKunyomi: う.む, う.まれる, うぶ-, む.す"
  answers:
    - 産
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6563
  prompt: "Meanings: scatter, disperse, spend\nOnyomi: サン\nKunyomi: ち.る, ち.らす, -ち.らす, ち.らかす"
  answers:
    - 散
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6b8b
  prompt: "Meanings: remainder, leftover, balance\nOnyomi: ザン, サン\nKunyomi: のこ.る, のこ.す, そこな.う, のこ.り"
  answers:
    - 残
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6c0f
  prompt: "Meanings: family name, surname, clan\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: うじ, -うじ"
  answers:
    - 氏
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-53f8
  prompt: "Meanings: director, official, govt office\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: つかさど.る"
  answers:
    - 司
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8a66
  prompt: "Meanings: test, try, attempt\nOnyomi: シ\nKunyomi: こころ.みる, ため.す"
  answers:
    - 試
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5150
  prompt: "Meanings: newborn babe, child, young of animals\nOnyomi: ジ, ニ, ゲイ\nKunyomi: こ, -こ, -っこ"
  answers:
    - 児
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6cbb
  prompt: "Meanings: reign, be at peace, calm down\nOnyomi: ジ, チ\nKunyomi: おさ.める, おさ.まる, なお.る, なお.す"
  answers:
    - 治
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6ecb
  prompt: "Meanings: nourishing, more & more, be luxuriant\nOnyomi: ジ, シ"
  answers:
    - 滋
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8f9e
  prompt: "Meanings: resign, word, term\nOnyomi: ジ\nKunyomi: や.める, いな.む"
  answers:
    - 辞
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9e7f
  prompt: "Meanings: deer\nOnyomi: ロク\nKunyomi: しか, か"
  answers:
    - 鹿
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5931
  prompt: "Meanings: lose, error, fault\nOnyomi: シツ\nKunyomi: うしな.う, う.せる"
  answers:
    - 失
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-501f
  prompt: "Meanings: borrow, rent\nOnyomi: シャク\nKunyomi: か.りる"
  answers:
    - 借
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7a2e
  prompt: "Meanings: species, kind, class\nOnyomi: シュ\nKunyomi: たね, -ぐさ"
  answers:
    - 種
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5468
  prompt: "Meanings: circumference, circuit, lap\nOnyomi: シュウ\nKunyomi: まわ.り"
  answers:
    - 周
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-795d
  prompt: "Meanings: celebrate, congratulate\nOnyomi: シュク, シュウ\nKunyomi: いわ.う"
  answers:
    - 祝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9806
  prompt: "Meanings: obey, order, turn\nOnyomi: ジュン"
  answers:
    - 順
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-521d
  prompt: "Meanings: first time, beginning\nOnyomi: ショ\nKunyomi: はじ.め, はじ.めて, はつ, はつ-"
  answers:
    - 初
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-677e
  prompt: "Meanings: pine tree\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: まつ"
  answers:
    - 松
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7b11
  prompt: "Meanings: laugh\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: わら.う, え.む"
  answers:
    - 笑
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5531
  prompt: "Meanings: chant, recite, call upon\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: とな.える"
  answers:
    - 唱
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-713c
  prompt: "Meanings: bake, burning\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: や.く, や.き, や.き-, -や.き"
  answers:
    - 焼
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7167
  prompt: "Meanings: illuminate, shine, compare\nOnyomi: ショウ\nKunyomi: て.る, て.らす, て.れる"
  answers:
    - 照
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-57ce
  prompt: "Meanings: castle\nOnyomi: ジョウ, セイ\nKunyomi: しろ"
  answers:
    - 城
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7e04
  prompt: "Meanings: straw rope, cord\nOnyomi: ジョウ\nKunyomi: なわ, ただ.す"
  answers:
    - 縄
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-81e3
  prompt: "Meanings: retainer, subject\nOnyomi: シン, ジン"
  answers:
    - 臣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4fe1
  prompt: "Meanings: faith, truth, fidelity\nOnyomi: シン"
  answers:
    - 信
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e95
  prompt: "Meanings: well, well crib, town\nOnyomi: セイ, ショウ\nKunyomi: い"
  answers:
    - 井
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6210
  prompt: "Meanings: turn into, become, get\nOnyomi: セイ, ジョウ\nKunyomi: な.る, な.す, -な.す"
  answers:
    - 成
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7701
  prompt: "Meanings: government ministry, conserve, omit\nOnyomi: セイ, ショウ\nKunyomi: かえり.みる, はぶ.く"
  answers:
    - 省
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6e05
  prompt: "Meanings: pure, purify, cleanse\nOnyomi: セイ, ショウ, シン\nKunyomi: きよ.い, きよ.まる, きよ.める"
  answers:
    - 清
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9759
  prompt: "Meanings: quiet\nOnyomi: セイ, ジョウ\nKunyomi: しず-, しず.か, しず.まる, しず.める"
  answers:
    - 静
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e2d
  prompt: "Meanings: seat, mat, occasion\nOnyomi: セキ\nKunyomi: むしろ"
  answers:
    - 席
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7a4d
  prompt: "Meanings: volume, product (x*y), acreage\nOnyomi: セキ\nKunyomi: つ.む, -づ.み, つ.もる, つ.もり"
  answers:
    - 積
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6298
  prompt: "Meanings: fold, break, fracture\nOnyomi: セツ, シャク\nKunyomi: お.る, おり, お.り, -お.り"
  answers:
    - 折
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7bc0
  prompt: "Meanings: node, season, period\nOnyomi: セツ, セチ\nKunyomi: ふし, -ぶし, のっと"
  answers:
    - 節
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8aac
  prompt: "Meanings: opinion, theory, explanation\nOnyomi: セツ, ゼイ\nKunyomi: と.く"
  answers:
    - 説
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6d45
  prompt: "Meanings: shallow, superficial, frivolous\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: あさ.い"
  answers:
    - 浅
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6226
  prompt: "Meanings: war, battle, match\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: いくさ, たたか.う, おのの.く, そよ.ぐ"
  answers:
    - 戦
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9078
  prompt: "Meanings: elect, select, choose\nOnyomi: セン\nKunyomi: えら.ぶ, え.る, よ.る"
  answers:
    - 選
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7136
  prompt: "Meanings: sort of thing, so, if so\nOnyomi: ゼン, ネン\nKunyomi: しか, しか.り, しか.し, さ"
  answers:
    - 然
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e89
  prompt: "Meanings: contend, dispute, argue\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: あらそ.う, いか.でか"
  answers:
    - 争
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5009
  prompt: "Meanings: godown, warehouse, storehouse\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: くら"
  answers:
    - 倉
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5de3
  prompt: "Meanings: nest, rookery, hive\nOnyomi: ソウ\nKunyomi: す, す.くう"
  answers:
    - 巣
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-675f
  prompt: "Meanings: bundle, sheaf, ream\nOnyomi: ソク\nKunyomi: たば, たば.ねる, つか, つか.ねる"
  answers:
    - 束
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5074
  prompt: "Meanings: side, lean, oppose\nOnyomi: ソク\nKunyomi: かわ, がわ, そば"
  answers:
    - 側
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d9a
  prompt: "Meanings: continue, series, sequel\nOnyomi: ゾク, ショク, コウ, キョウ\nKunyomi: つづ.く, つづ.ける, つぐ.ない"
  answers:
    - 続
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5352
  prompt: "Meanings: graduate, soldier, private\nOnyomi: ソツ, シュツ\nKunyomi: そっ.する, お.える, お.わる, ついに"
  answers:
    - 卒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5b6b
  prompt: "Meanings: grandchild, descendants\nOnyomi: ソン\nKunyomi: まご"
  answers:
    - 孫
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e2f
  prompt: "Meanings: sash, belt, obi\nOnyomi: タイ\nKunyomi: お.びる, おび"
  answers:
    - 帯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-968a
  prompt: "Meanings: regiment, party, company\nOnyomi: タイ"
  answers:
    - 隊
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9054
  prompt: "Meanings: accomplished, reach, arrive\nOnyomi: タツ, ダ\nKunyomi: -たち"
  answers:
    - 達
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5358
  prompt: "Meanings: simple, one, single\nOnyomi: タン\nKunyomi: ひとえ"
  answers:
    - 単
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7f6e
  prompt: "Meanings: placement, put, set\nOnyomi: チ\nKunyomi: お.く, -お.き"
  answers:
    - 置
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ef2
  prompt: "Meanings: go-between, relationship\nOnyomi: チュウ\nKunyomi: なか"
  answers:
    - 仲
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6c96
  prompt: "Meanings: open sea, offing, rise high into sky\nOnyomi: チュウ\nKunyomi: おき, おきつ, ちゅう.する, わく"
  answers:
    - 沖
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5146
  prompt: "Meanings: portent, 10**12, trillion\nOnyomi: チョウ\nKunyomi: きざ.す, きざ.し"
  answers:
    - 兆
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f4e
  prompt: "Meanings: lower, short, humble\nOnyomi: テイ\nKunyomi: ひく.い, ひく.める, ひく.まる"
  answers:
    - 低
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e95
  prompt: "Meanings: bottom, sole, depth\nOnyomi: テイ\nKunyomi: そこ"
  answers:
    - 底
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7684
  prompt: "Meanings: bull's eye, mark, target\nOnyomi: テキ\nKunyomi: まと"
  answers:
    - 的
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5178
  prompt: "Meanings: code, ceremony, law\nOnyomi: テン, デン\nKunyomi: ふみ, のり"
  answers:
    - 典
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f1d
  prompt: "Meanings: transmit, go along, walk along\nOnyomi: デン, テン\nKunyomi: つた.わる, つた.える, つた.う, つだ.う"
  answers:
    - 伝
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5f92
  prompt: "Meanings: on foot, junior, emptiness\nOnyomi: ト\nKunyomi: いたずら, あだ"
  answers:
    - 徒
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-52aa
  prompt: "Meanings: toil, diligent, as much as possible\nOnyomi: ド\nKunyomi: つと.める"
  answers:
    - 努
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-706f
  prompt: "Meanings: lamp, a light, light\nOnyomi: トウ\nKunyomi: ひ, ほ-, ともしび, とも.す"
  answers:
    - 灯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-50cd
  prompt: "Meanings: work, (kokuji)\nOnyomi: ドウ\nKunyomi: はたら.く"
  answers:
    - 働
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7279
  prompt: "Meanings: special\nOnyomi: トク"
  answers:
    - 特
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5fb3
  prompt: "Meanings: benevolence, virtue, goodness\nOnyomi: トク"
  answers:
    - 徳
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6803
  prompt: "Meanings: horse chestnut, (kokuji)\nKunyomi: とち"
  answers:
    - 栃
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5948
  prompt: "Meanings: Nara, what?\nOnyomi: ナ, ナイ, ダイ\nKunyomi: いかん, からなし"
  answers:
    - 奈
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-68a8
  prompt: "Meanings: pear tree\nOnyomi: リ\nKunyomi: なし"
  answers:
    - 梨
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-71b1
  prompt: "Meanings: heat, temperature, fever\nOnyomi: ネツ\nKunyomi: あつ.い"
  answers:
    - 熱
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5ff5
  prompt: "Meanings: wish, sense, idea\nOnyomi: ネン"
  answers:
    - 念
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6557
  prompt: "Meanings: failure, defeat, reversal\nOnyomi: ハイ\nKunyomi: やぶ.れる"
  answers:
    - 敗
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6885
  prompt: "Meanings: plum\nOnyomi: バイ\nKunyomi: うめ"
  answers:
    - 梅
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-535a
  prompt: "Meanings: Dr., command, esteem\nOnyomi: ハク, バク"
  answers:
    - 博
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-962a
  prompt: "Meanings: heights, slope\nOnyomi: ハン\nKunyomi: さか"
  answers:
    - 阪
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-98ef
  prompt: "Meanings: meal, boiled rice\nOnyomi: ハン\nKunyomi: めし"
  answers:
    - 飯
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-98db
  prompt: "Meanings: fly, skip (pages), scatter\nOnyomi: ヒ\nKunyomi: と.ぶ, と.ばす, -と.ばす"
  answers:
    - 飛
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5fc5
  prompt: "Meanings: invariably, certain, inevitable\nOnyomi: ヒツ\nKunyomi: かなら.ず"
  answers:
    - 必
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7968
  prompt: "Meanings: ballot, label, ticket\nOnyomi: ヒョウ"
  answers:
    - 票
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6a19
  prompt: "Meanings: signpost, seal, mark\nOnyomi: ヒョウ\nKunyomi: しるべ, しるし"
  answers:
    - 標
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4e0d
  prompt: "Meanings: negative, non-, bad\nOnyomi: フ, ブ"
  answers:
    - 不
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-592b
  prompt: "Meanings: husband, man\nOnyomi: フ, フウ, ブ\nKunyomi: おっと, それ"
  answers:
    - 夫
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ed8
  prompt: "Meanings: adhere, attach, refer to\nOnyomi: フ\nKunyomi: つ.ける, -つ.ける, -づ.ける, つ.け"
  answers:
    - 付
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5e9c
  prompt: "Meanings: borough, urban prefecture, govt office\nOnyomi: フ"
  answers:
    - 府
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-961c
  prompt: "Meanings: hill, mound, left village radical (no. 170)\nOnyomi: フ, フウ"
  answers:
    - 阜
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5bcc
  prompt: "Meanings: wealth, enrich, abundant\nOnyomi: フ, フウ\nKunyomi: と.む, とみ"
  answers:
    - 富
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-526f
  prompt: "Meanings: vice-, assistant, aide\nOnyomi: フク"
  answers:
    - 副
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5175
  prompt: "Meanings: soldier, private, troops\nOnyomi: ヘイ, ヒョウ\nKunyomi: つわもの"
  answers:
    - 兵
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5225
  prompt: "Meanings: separate, branch off, diverge\nOnyomi: ベツ\nKunyomi: わか.れる, わ.ける"
  answers:
    - 別
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8fba
  prompt: "Meanings: environs, boundary, border\nOnyomi: ヘン\nKunyomi: あた.り, ほと.り, -べ"
  answers:
    - 辺
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5909
  prompt: "Meanings: unusual, change, strange\nOnyomi: ヘン\nKunyomi: か.わる, か.わり, か.える"
  answers:
    - 変
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4fbf
  prompt: "Meanings: convenience, facility, excrement\nOnyomi: ベン, ビン\nKunyomi: たよ.り"
  answers:
    - 便
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5305
  prompt: "Meanings: wrap, pack up, cover\nOnyomi: ホウ\nKunyomi: つつ.む, くる.む"
  answers:
    - 包
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6cd5
  prompt: "Meanings: method, law, rule\nOnyomi: ホウ, ハッ, ホッ, フラン\nKunyomi: のり"
  answers:
    - 法
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-671b
  prompt: "Meanings: ambition, full moon, hope\nOnyomi: ボウ, モウ\nKunyomi: のぞ.む, もち"
  answers:
    - 望
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7267
  prompt: "Meanings: breed, care for, shepherd\nOnyomi: ボク\nKunyomi: まき"
  answers:
    - 牧
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-672b
  prompt: "Meanings: end, close, tip\nOnyomi: マツ, バツ\nKunyomi: すえ, うら, うれ"
  answers:
    - 末
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6e80
  prompt: "Meanings: full, fullness, enough\nOnyomi: マン, バン\nKunyomi: み.ちる, み.つ, み.たす"
  answers:
    - 満
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-672a
  prompt: "Meanings: un-, not yet, hitherto\nOnyomi: ミ, ビ\nKunyomi: いま.だ, ま.だ, ひつじ"
  answers:
    - 未
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6c11
  prompt: "Meanings: people, nation, subjects\nOnyomi: ミン\nKunyomi: たみ"
  answers:
    - 民
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7121
  prompt: "Meanings: nothingness, none, ain't\nOnyomi: ム, ブ\nKunyomi: な.い"
  answers:
    - 無
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-7d04
  prompt: "Meanings: promise, approximately, shrink\nOnyomi: ヤク\nKunyomi: つづ.まる, つづ.める, つづま.やか"
  answers:
    - 約
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-52c7
  prompt: "Meanings: courage, cheer up, be in high spirits\nOnyomi: ユウ\nKunyomi: いさ.む"
  answers:
    - 勇
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8981
  prompt: "Meanings: need, main point, essence\nOnyomi: ヨウ\nKunyomi: い.る, かなめ"
  answers:
    - 要
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-990a
  prompt: "Meanings: foster, bring up, rear\nOnyomi: ヨウ, リョウ\nKunyomi: やしな.う"
  answers:
    - 養
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6d74
  prompt: "Meanings: bathe, be favored with, bask in\nOnyomi: ヨク\nKunyomi: あ.びる, あ.びせる"
  answers:
    - 浴
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-5229
  prompt: "Meanings: profit, advantage, benefit\nOnyomi: リ\nKunyomi: き.く"
  answers:
    - 利
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9678
  prompt: "Meanings: land, six\nOnyomi: リク, ロク\nKunyomi: おか"
  answers:
    - 陸
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-826f
  prompt: "Meanings: good, pleasing, skilled\nOnyomi: リョウ\nKunyomi: よ.い, -よ.い, い.い, -い.い"
  answers:
    - 良
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-6599
  prompt: "Meanings: fee, materials\nOnyomi: リョウ"
  answers:
    - 料
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-91cf
  prompt: "Meanings: quantity, measure, weight\nOnyomi: リョウ\nKunyomi: はか.る"
  answers:
    - 量
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8f2a
  prompt: "Meanings: wheel, ring, circle\nOnyomi: リン\nKunyomi: わ"
  answers:
    - 輪
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-985e
  prompt: "Meanings: sort, kind, variety\nOnyomi: ルイ\nKunyomi: たぐ.い"
  answers:
    - 類
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4ee4
  prompt: "Meanings: orders, laws, command\nOnyomi: レイ"
  answers:
    - 令
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-51b7
  prompt: "Meanings: cool, cold (beer, person), chill\nOnyomi: レイ\nKunyomi: つめ.たい, ひ.える, ひ.や, ひ.ややか"
  answers:
    - 冷
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-4f8b
  prompt: "Meanings: example, custom, usage\nOnyomi: レイ\nKunyomi: たと.える"
  answers:
    - 例
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9023
  prompt: "Meanings: take along, lead, join\nOnyomi: レン\nKunyomi: つら.なる, つら.ねる, つ.れる, -づ.れ"
  answers:
    - 連
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-8001
  prompt: "Meanings: old man, old age, grow old\nOnyomi: ロウ\nKunyomi: お.いる, ふ.ける"
  answers:
    - 老
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-52b4
  prompt: "Meanings: labor, thank for, reward for\nOnyomi: ロウ\nKunyomi: ろう.する, いたわ.る, いた.ずき, ねぎら"
  answers:
    - 労
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: k-joyo-9332
  prompt: "Meanings: record\nOnyomi: ロク\nKunyomi: しる.す, と.る"
  answers:
    - 録
  hint: ""
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
